

FULL STACK WEB AND APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Details

6145928914 drae7299@gmail.com

Links

Project 1

Code Quiz

Password Gen

Day Planner

Skills

Problem Solving

Interpersonal Skills

Ability to Multitask

Leadership Skills

Decision Making

Creativity

Adaptability

Customer Service

Ability to Work in a Team

Microsoft Office

Computer Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Fast Learner

Dedicated team player

Strong Communication Skills

Profile

Passionate Full Stack Web and App Dev with over 15 years experience in Education, Marketing and Management. Andre has excelled in all roles he has had and used them all as an opportunity to grow and develop his skills in the work force. Currently Andre is progressing quickly through multiple coding languages with a strong JavaScript focus. He is excited to take on a new Developer role and help drive the productivity of his future company.

Employment History

Sr. Microsoft Market Manager, Microsoft, Columbus

SEPTEMBER 2016 - PRESENT

Maintains a market of 70+ stores and uses relationship skills to drive sales for the Brand. Trains, sells and facilitates training sessions for employees in store. Maintains strict set of monthly and quarterly KPI goals as well as software presence. Travels to other states and cities to present to larger audiences for market and regional training's as well via Zoom and Teams for Channel and Market executive managers.

Percussion Instructor, Westerville City Schools, Westerville

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT

- Train 8th-12th grade students
- Help prepare for state competitions and collegiate auditions
- Provide private lessons
- Provide in school training during music classes
- Travel with band to Friday night games

Education

Full Stack Web Dev, Ohio State University, Columbus, Columbus

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Front end and Back end
- JavaScript focus
- MongoDB
- React
- Node.js
- CSS
- HTML
- MySQL

Associates of Arts, Columbus State Community College, Columbus

SEPTEMBER 2010 - JANUARY 2012

- Prerequisites
- Basic classes for 2 years